In order to make it easier to arrange, first hide the window in the library.
Click on the 2D arrangement tool to reset the 3D window to the 2D window.
Click on the display arrangement icon in the 3D window vertical view menu.
You can see that the virtual model has appeared around the blue points that are used to arrange the panels.
Press Ctrl A to select all panels. After clicking on the panel, the positioning ball that can control the position of the panel will appear.
Drag the green axis of the positioning ball to move all panels to the position of the arrangement point without blocking.
Drag the other axis on the positioning ball to move in other directions.
Click and drag the yellow square in the positioning ball to move in the plane.
Drag the circle on the positioning ball to move in the plane.
Click and drag the circle to move in the plane.
Press Ctrl C to cancel the procedure.
The default positioning ball is based on the perspective of the lens.
In the menu bar in the 3D background, you can change the positioning ball coordinates.
The horizontal coordinates are based on the horizontal coordinates of the selected object.
The horizontal coordinates are based on the
The horizontal coordinates are fixed.
When arranging a board, its symmetrical board will also be arranged in the same way.
Since the board has a positive and a negative side, please check the board transparency when arranging the back of the board to prevent mistakes.
After arranging the board, you can adjust its properties in the property editor.
Drag and drop the adjustment axis to rotate or move the board.
When a board property is modified, the other symmetrical board will also be modified.
Adjusting the axis can make the board close or far from the model.
Changing the direction can make the board rotate in one direction.
You can also use the positioning tool to adjust the position of the board after arranging.
However, the position of the positioning tool will not be applied to the symmetrical board.
Press the Shift key and click on the board, you can select more boards.
It is recommended that if you use the positioning tool to modify the 3D position, you can modify the position of two boards at the same time.
You can see that if you continue to display the arrangement points after arranging the board, it will be more inconvenient.
Therefore, after arranging the board, please hide the arrangement points.
If you have any questions, please leave a comment.
I would like to make the video shorter in the future, so I will do my best.
If you have any questions, please feel free to write a comment, so that it would not be a problem.
You can also adjust the position of the board.
You can express the position of the board by changing the position of the board.
You can also use the position of the board to adjust the position of the board.